socialsecurity-disability.org 2013-01-16

# Privacy Policy

**Effective January 1, 2010**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the SocialSecurity-Disability.org website. On some pages, you can complete a free, online evaluation to be contacted by a disability attorney or advocate regarding your claim. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Date of Birth
  * Case Description

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

  * Claimant Name
  * Claimant Address
  * Claimant Email Address
  * Claimant Phone Number
  * Claimant Date of Birth
  * Case Description

  * Your Name
  * Your Address
  * Your Email Address
  * Your Phone Number

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when completing an evaluation only to assist you with your potential disability claim. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to have your case evaluated by a disability attorney or advocate. There is no cost for this evaluation. 

We use the information you provide about someone when completing an evaluation only to assist that individual with his/her potential disability claim. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to have the case evaluated by a disability attorney or advocate. There is no cost for this evaluation. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to learn more about visitors to our website. For example, we may find out that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at support@socialsecurity-disability.org To remove yourself from our contact list: http://www.socialsecurity-disability.org/form/unsubscribe
